McConnell, John W. Additional Arbitration Files 5961
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Arbitrations: 1979-1982 (Box 10)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Council of Utility Contractors, Inc. and Laborers International Union of North America Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - General School District and Civil Service Employees Association Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Rome City School and Rome Teachers Association Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Blue Cross of Western NY and Office and Professional Employees Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Includes: Union membership transactions, and blue cross/shield office rules
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - E.I. Du Pont DE Nemours and Company and Defender Union Arbitration, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - E.I. Du Pont De Nemours and Company and Defender Union Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - E.I. Du Pont De Nemours and Company and Defender Union Arbitration, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Arbitrations: 1980-1983 (Box 11)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carries Arbitration, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - US Postal Service and National Association for Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - US Postal Service and America Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1977-1982 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1973-1982 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - US Postal Service and America Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Arbitrations: 1980-1982 (Box 12)
  - Weedsport Central School District and Weedsport Teachers Association Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Capital Newspaper Division and Albany Printing Press Division Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - City of Buffalo and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees Union Arbitration, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - City Of Buffalo and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees Union Arbitration, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Simmonds Precision Co. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Arbitration, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - NY Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America Arbitration, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - NY Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - City of Syracuse and Police Benevolent Association Arbitration, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Kennedy Valve Division ITT Grinnell Valve Co. and United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America Arbitration, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Bendix Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - County of Wyoming and Civil Service Employee Association Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - NYS Dept. of Taxation and Finance and Public Employees Federation Arbitration, 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - US Postal Service and United Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Odessa Montour School District and Odessa Montour Teachers Association Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Sweet Home Central School District and Sweet Home Education Association Arbitration, 1979-1984 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Arbitrations: 1977-1983 (Box 13)
  - City of Syracuse, NY and Police Benevolent Association Arbitration, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Jamestown Board Education and Jamestown Teachers Association Arbitration, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Elmira City School District and The Custodial, Maintenance, and Cafeteria Employees Unit Arbitration, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - South Jefferson Central School District and Civil Service Employee Association Arbitration, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - City of Boston and American Federation Of State, County and Municipal Employees Arbitration, 1977-1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Newfane Central School District and Newfane Teachers Association, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Midstate Telephone Corp. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Mount Markham School District and Mount Markham Teachers Association Arbitration, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Samaritan-Keep Nursing Home, Inc. and NYS Nurse Association Arbitration, 1978-1983 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Pipe Welding Supply Co. and Teamsters Local 529 Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Cincinnatus Central School District and Cincinnatus Education Association Arbitration, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Webster Central School District and Webster Teachers Association, 1982-1985 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Gates Chili Central School and Gates Teachers Association Arbitration, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Black Clawson Co. and International Molders and Allied Workers Union Arbitration, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    Includes: Newspapers
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Arbitrations: 1983-1985 (Box 14)
  - US Postal Service and National Association Of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - US Postal Service and National Association Of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Includes: Photo documents
  - US Postal Service and National Association Of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - US Postal Service and National Association Of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - US Postal Service and National Association Of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - US Postal Service and National Association Of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983-1985 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - US Postal Services Arbitrations between American Postal Workers Union and National Assoc. Of Letter Carriers, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - City Elmira, NY and Civil Service Employees Association Arbitration, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - NYS Dept. of Correctional Services and Correctional Officer, Frank Yancy, Grievant, Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - NYS Dept. of Correctional Services and Correctional Officer, Frank Yancy, Grievant, Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Arbitrations: 1983-1986 (Box 15)
  - Dept. Of Environmental Conservation and American Fed. Of State, County and Municipal Employees Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Includes: street sign/ or metal poster
  - Dept. Of Environmental Conservation and American Fed. Of State, County and Municipal Employees Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Seneca Falls Central School District and Seneca Falls Employees Association Arbitration, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Marcellus Central School District and Marcellus Faculty Association Arbitration, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Rome Cable Corp. and International Association of Machinist and Aerospace Workers Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Keith Clark Inc. and Sidney Typography Local Union Arbitration, 1983-1986 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Includes: photo documents
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Otsego Northern Catskills BOCES and Non-Teaching Employees Organization Arbitration, 1983-1986 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Includes: gloves a worker used as evidence
  - Harpursville Central School District and Harpursville Teachers Association Arbitration, 1983-1986 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Harpursville Central School District and Harpursville Teachers Association Arbitration, 1983-1986 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Arbitrations: 1983-1985 (Box 16)
  - State of Connecticut and Connecticut State Police Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Moravia Central School District and Civil Service Employees Association Arbitration, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Includes: sketch of floor plans
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Onondaga Central School District and Onondaga Central Non-Instructional Staff Assoc. Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Includes: school calendar
  - Onondaga Central School District and Onondaga Central Non-Instructional Staff Assoc. Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - St. Lawrence County and Deputy Sheriffs' Association Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Includes: floor plans
  - Mohawk Central School District and Mohawk Central School Teachers Association Arbitration, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Midstate Telephone Corp. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Midstate Telephone Corp. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Sterling Drug Co. and International Chemical Workers Union Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    microcassette tapes - were moved to the media case, now boxes 30 and 31
- Arbitrations: 1983-1985 (Box 17)
  - Onondaga Central School District and Onondaga Central School Non-Instructional Staff Association Arbitration, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - US Postal Workers and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - State of Connecticut and Connecticut State Police Union Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - State of Connecticut and Connecticut State Police Union Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Includes: hotel receipt and airline ticket
  - State of Connecticut and Connecticut State Police Union Arbitration, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - NYS Electrical and Gas Corp. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Includes: photo documents and drawings
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Addison Central School District and Addison Teachers Association Arbitration, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Ithaca City School District and Ithaca City School District Employees Association Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Addison Central School District and Addison Teachers Association Arbitration, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Ilion Central School District and Ilion Teachers Association Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Arbitrations: 1983-1986 (Box 18)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Will and Baumer Candle Co. and IUE Local 321 Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Arbitration with International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried and Machine Workers (IUE)
  - BOCES First Supervisory District and BOCES Erie County Management Association Arbitration, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - US Postal Workers and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Lewiston Porter School and Lewiston Porter United Teachers Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Kraft Inc. Retail Food Group and Food Store Employees Local 34 Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Bendix Corp. Fluid Power Division and United Steel Workers of America Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Arbitrations: 1983-1984 (Box 19)
  - City of Elmira and Professional Fire Fighters Association Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Includes: newspaper articles, and employee handbook
  - City of Elmira and Professional Fire Fighters Association Arbitration, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - City of Elmira and Professional Fire Fighters Association Arbitration, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - City of Elmira and Professional Fire Fighters Association Arbitration, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - City of Elmira and Professional Fire Fighters Association Arbitration, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - NY Air Break Co. and International Molders and Allied Workers Union Arbitration, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Niagara Genesee and Vicinity Carpenters Local No.280 Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Niagara Genesee and Vicinity Carpenters Local No.280 Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Niagara Genesee and Vicinity Carpenters Local No.280 Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Frewsburg Central School and Frewsburg Faculty Association Arbitration, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Mohawk Valley Community College and Mohawk Valley Community College Professional Association Arbitration, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Mohawk Valley Community College and Mohawk Valley Community College Professional Association Arbitration, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Arbitrations: 1982-1985 (Box 20)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - American LaFrance, Division of A-T-O Inc. and International Association of Machinist and Aerospace Workers Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Loretto Geriatric Center and Service Employees International Arbitration, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fair Banks Co. and United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America Arbitration, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Includes: copied posters
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - City of Syracuse and Police Benevolent Association Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 14)